Fengyun Lu

Web3 Security Engineer

Ambitious, Experienced, Ready for Advancement







rapig1915@gmail.com (+86) 13804157550 Yiwu, Zhejiang, China



ABOUT

Starting my career as a software engineer, I quickly became fascinated by the world of web3. I've eagerly learned the basics of blockchain and smart contract development, gaining some practical experience with a small startup.

Understanding the vital importance of security, I've focused the last three years on working as a security engineer.

As we move into this new and exciting era, I am keen to play a key role in the industry and look forward to exploring its vast potential.

EXPERIENCE

2023 - NOW

Web3 Security Engineer · Reserve 🧷

- Conduct security audit on utility products
- Communicate with development team
- Automate vulnerablity check using private tools
- Develop and maintain audit pipeline

Audit

Rust

Ethereum

Base

Security

Smart Contract Auditor 7

- \$162k+ in earnings
- Placed 1st in Code4rena GoGoPool audit
- Placed 3rd in Code4rena Paraspace audit
- Ranked #17 on Code4rena all-time leaderboard

Code4rena Solidity Security Solana Go Vyper

2021 - 2022

Blockchain Developer · Mogle 7

- Build freelance product for decentralized earning Explored Solidity and web3 concepts
- Began career in the blockchain industry at a DApp development startup
- Mastered smart contract development
- Worked in a focused team of three
- Implemented decentralized storage, consensus mechanisms, and Layer 2 scaling solutions

Smart Contracts Solidity Ethereum Hardhat Rollups

2014 — 2021

Web / Mobile Developer · IDC/Games 7

- Progressed from junior web developer to proficient contributor
- Specialized in C#, Python, and JavaScript for web and mobile development
- Led development of web services, admin dashboards, and landing portals
- Collaborated closely with the CTO
- Implemented progressive development patterns
- Provided valuable insights for decision-making
- Enhanced workflows and adopted innovative strategies for efficiency

Python C# JavaScript AWS React Native

View Full Résumé 7

PROJECTS



IDC/Games 7

IDC Games is a multi-language digital PC game distribution platform that integrates user registration, in-game payments, esports, and a loyalty program, for every published game in the platform.

± 200k+ installs



Reserve 7

A permissionless platform to launch and govern 1:1 asset-backed currencies called RTokens.

★ 119.3K Followers

Web3 RToken Yield Staking

EDUCATION

Tsinghua University

GPA 4.0, Grade A
Bachelor's degree in Computer Science
English Proficiency with TOEFL score 100